A hundred more push-ups.
I-I'm melting...
Another ten minutes.
Thirty more squats.
Potato Killer
Alone at last...
Time to eat some-
Meow Meow
Eek!
That's all you get for dinner tonight.
Plus-Sized Elf
The Beefy Soldier and Remnants of a Dream
Here.
Human... I owe you one.
Well, she is losing weight...
But this diet of hers isn't healthy at all...
That hits the spot!
Human? What's with the grumpy face?
Huh?
You can tell me if something's bothering you.
We're friends, after all.
She's the one who's suffering, and yet...
What the hell am I doing...?
Be ye reconciled to spuds
Stand up.
Your break is over.
It's time for sword practice.
O-okay!
Human?
Never mind.
Now get into position.
We'll start with a thousand swings.
G-got it!
One!
Two!
Three!
Put your back into it!
But it's hard on an empty stomach...
Quit complaining!
You shouldn't be tired yet!
Come on, keep going.
Human...?
Can you step aside, please?
I refuse!
Elfuda is MY patient!
I'M the one responsible for
helping her lose weight!
So, no! I will NOT step aside!
And I can't convince you otherwise?
I wasn't sure what to do
after our conversation...
But I never should have
doubted myself in the first place.
Because the solution was clear all along!
The way you try to wear her down
and break her spirit isn't right!
I see...
Then you leave me no choice.
H-human, watch out!
Please don't do this, Auntie!
I'll move you by force!
Didn't even bat an eye...
Still, that doesn't necessarily mean
your methods are effective-
His methods ARE effective!
He helped me lose weight once before.
It's my lifestyle that's the real problem!
If you know that, then fix it.
Eek, I'm sorry!
I-it's just...
I put my faith in the human!
And in return, he's given me lots of knowledge
and taught me a bunch of techniques!
Which is why...
if I'm going to lose weight again,
it'll be with HIS guidance!
Telling me exactly what's on her mind...
She's never done that before.
Fine.
The human can take it from here.
Auntie...!
I'll report the situation back to Big Sis.
Be sure to follow the human's advice
and make an effort to form good habits.
Okay, Auntie.
I'll keep a close eye on Elfuda's progress
so she can lose weight in a healthy way!
Please do.
And try to pay your mother a visit
from time to time.
Take care of yourself.
Uh-oh...
Wh-what happened, Auntie?!
I can't get through the gate.
What?!
I wonder why...
THAT'S why!
Plus-Sized Elf
Plus-Sized Elf!
She's already started the intensive training...
Ah, the human and the spherical elf.
What are you up to?
Oh, Kuroeda.
We decided to join my auntie
for her training session.
Speaking of which...
what was that about "spherical"?
I ♥ GREASE
Wha-?! You look...!
How is this possible?!
Maybe YOU should consider
training with my auntie, too.
If you want to look as good as I do.
Hm? I certainly don't mind.
You're right.
Perhaps that would be a good idea.
In that case, take this.
As thanks for the advice.
Valid for a free order of fries
A coupon for French fries?
Fries aren't a part of Elfuda's diet right-
Guess I was wrong about you!
Whoa, hold on!
You worked so hard to lose weight!
Yeah, exactly!
Where's the harm in ONE order of fries?
It's a little reward for myself!
French fries, French fries!
I don't really remember much from that day...
Y-you don't?
Is that... our elven friend?
Sh-she's so slim...!
Flatter than a flounder!
Why, she must've worked herself to the bone!
I can't let her outshine me like that!
Me neither!
Same here!
Mega-size Fries
Starting today, our legendary "Mega-Size Fries"
are back by popular demand!
Would you like to try some?
L-legendary...?!
Thank you, come again!
I can't pass up a legendary opportunity!
If I don't get to be happy,
then neither do you.
So ya want a gemstone to make
a pwetty neckwace, eh?
I gotcha. Well, since you're a fwiend...
My wecommendation is this turquoise.
Oooh, sparkly!
I like it! How much?
I'll give ya a nice discount...
So expensive! Can you go a little lower?
If there's one fing cylopes know,
it's how to spot a quawity cwystal.
Fwashin' her a fake ain't gonna fwy.
Since I'm sellin' her the weal deal,
I gotta milk her for all she's worf!
Look, I'll lift you way up high!
So... deal?
I ain't makin' it cheaper for THIS!
I'm an entrepweneur, ya bozo!
I caught you...
I knew it. You are trying to be
her mommy, aren't you?!
Oh no, looks like she's itching for a fight...
Let's continue this another time.
W-wait a second!
Pwease don't weave me alone with the ogre!
Huh...?
I'll give ya the turquoise
for twenty percent off!
Sorry, what was that?
Grr...
Firty percent off!
Now get her cwazy ass outta my park!
Your offer has been accepted.
It's time to settle which of us
is the mightier mommy!
I don't care a whole lot about
being a mother, but...
I want that gemstone.
Brand new snack flavors!
Come and get your free samples!
Potato & Cheese
Here you go, ma'am!
It's my lucky day!
You volunteered to train with me
and yet you're quitting already?
No one told me... it was going to be...
this intense...
Another hundred squats to go.
How do you expect to be an
accomplished mage with such weak legs?
My legs have nothing to do with it!
Where is the Dragon Slenderer?
The dragon?!
When the hell did you get here?!
"Dragon Slenderer"?
It's her nickname for the human.
He isn't home?
Unfortunate, indeed.
Then you shall provide me warmth.
Warmth?
It was cold outside, so warm me up.
You must be joking!
Seriously, who died and made you king?
You have the audacity to defy
an apex predator such as I?
All that blubber ought to keep you
warm enough, you pudgy lizard!
You shall rue the day...
you dared to cross me!
Once the ogre starts to swow down,
I'll punch her wights out!
If I get the final bwow,
the cyclops pays full pwice!
You're wide open for a body shot!
Have some payback!
She's staggered! Now's my chance!
Fatality incoming!
Are you okay, pipsqueak?!
You shouldn't intervene in a fight,
it's dangerous!
But I'm relieved you didn't get hurt.
My cwothes beg to differ...
The human's apartment is nearby.
Let's head there.
'Kay.
This was all your fault...
Warm...
Good thing the human lives close to the park.
Yup, yup.
Yo, human! Sorry to barge in.
Why are you naked?
Hey, I'm home!
What's going on here?!
I was trying to do my usual
strength training regimen...
I just wanted to buy a pretty gemstone...
Just look at you sad sacks...
More rolls than a bakery!
Pathetic!
Maybe you guys ought to be a little more
ambitious and try having some self-control!
Don't talk down to us just because-
You're back to the same size as before!
Huh?
Care to explain yourself?
Whaaat? What for?
Massage Relaxation
Beauty  Health  Diet
But why would you eat that many French fries?
I mean, they were there, so...
that's the best I've got.
Perhaps I was wrong to trust
the human with your care.
Eek!
I-it's fine!
The human can help me lose weight!
Don't worry.
I'm committed to giving her
the support she needs.
I'm in your hands once again... Naoe!